eurweb.com 2019-03-31

# Our Privacy Policy | EURweb

**Information we collect and how we use it**

EURweb.com collects data about your activities that does not personally or directly identify you when you visit our website. This information may include the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, the products you purchase, or your location information associated with your IP address. We use the information we collect to serve you more relevant advertisements (referred to as “Retargeting”). We collect information about where you saw the ads we serve you and what ads you clicked on.  
We do not target ads to you based on sensitive health data, though, where permitted by law, we do work with health and fitness companies and may show you more relevant ads based on your perceived interest in these topics.  
EURweb.com may target ads based on data provided by Advertisers or partners alone or in combination with the data we collect ourselves. Any data used to serve targeted advertisements is de-identified and is not used to personally or directly identify you. We require third parties, including Publishers, to provide notice and obtain appropriate consent, where required by applicable law.

**Third parties on our website and our advertiser’ websites**

In order to allow EURweb.com to reach the best inventory online, we work with third party advertising companies (our “Advertising Partners”) to help us recognize you and serve relevant advertisements to you when you visit a website or online service in their network. We also work with Advertising Partners who help us recognize you across different devices in order to show you relevant advertisements. Our Advertising Partners may collect information about your activities on our website, our Advertisers’ websites, and other websites or online services in their networks. We also work with third party companies to assist us with website analytics such as evaluating the use and operation of our website so that we can continue to enhance the website and our services.

**Technologies we and our third party advertising partners use**

EURweb.com uses technologies such as cookies and pixels to keep track of your activities on our website and our Advertiser’s websites, and to serve you more relevant advertisements. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your device for record-keeping purposes. Session cookies expire when you close your browser. Persistent cookies remain on your device for an extended period of time. We and our third party partners use session cookies and persistent cookies to make it easier for you to navigate and enhance the experience of our site, and to monitor and evaluate our website’s operation and use.  
We use persistent cookies to keep track of your activities when you visit our website or our Advertisers’ websites, and to serve you relevant advertisements. Our Advertising Partners also place persistent cookies on your device when you visit our website or our Advertisers’ websites in order to help us recognize you and serve relevant advertisements to you when you visit their website or online service or websites in their networks. EURweb.com’s policy is that our Advertising Partners only collect information that does not personally or directly identify you via these cookies and we will cease working with partners found violating this policy. You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. You may also decline our cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of our website.

**Your choices regarding relevant advertisements**

We believe in giving you control over which ads you see. You may opt out of having your data collected from this device for the purpose of receiving Retargeted ads from EURweb.com (whether served by us or on our behalf). You may also opt out of receiving relevant ads from some of our Advertising Partners. If you delete your cookies you will need to opt out again. Further, if you use multiple browsers or devices, you will need to execute this opt out on each browser or device.

**How we share your information**

We may share your information with:

  * Service providers under contract who help with parts of our business operations, such as fraud prevention, bill collection, marketing, and technology services. We may share your information with service providers who assist us with serving relevant ads to you. We require by contract that our service providers only use your information in connection with the services they perform for us and not for their own benefit.
  * We may share aggregated non-identifiable information with Publishers or our Advertisers, such as the number of users who visit a Publisher website or the number of users who clicked on a particular advertisement. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of the website publishers that you visit to learn about their data collection practices. We do not provide information to our Advertisers about your activities. However, when you view or interact with a Retargeted ad, the Advertiser may infer that you engaged in the activities on its site that qualified you to receive the ad.
  * Companies that EURweb.com merges with or that acquire EURweb.com.
  * Other third parties with your consent or direction to do so.
  * We may share information about you if necessary to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order, or government request, or to protect the rights of EURweb.com or others.

**How we share personal information with other parties**

We may share your personal information with:

  * Service providers under contract who assist us with our business operations, such as fraud prevention, bill collection, marketing, and technology services. Our service providers are only authorized to use your information in connection with the services they perform for us and not for their own benefit.
  * Credit bureaus to report outstanding negative balance accounts, as allowed by law.
  * Companies that EURWeb.com merges with or that acquire EURweb.com. In this event, we will notify you before your information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * Other third parties with your consent or direction to do so.
  * We may share information about you if necessary to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order, or government request, or to protect the rights of EURweb.com or others.

**How you can access or change your personal information**

If you are located in the European Economic Area, you may have the right to request access to and receive information about the personal information we maintain about you, update and correct inaccuracies in your personal information and have the information blocked or deleted, as appropriate. The right to access personal information may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements. You also have the right to opt out, free of charge, from the processing of your personal information for marketing purposes. All requests for access, rectification, blocking and opting-out must be made in writing, signed, dated and accompanied by a copy of your ID card.

**How we protect personal information**  
We employ reasonable and appropriate security measures such as maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable security requirements, including US federal and state regulations. We use computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption; we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files; and we authorize access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities. All credit card information is encrypted with 128-bit SSL encryption before it is transmitted across the network. However, no security system is foolproof and we cannot guarantee the security of your information.

**Unsupervised children**

Children 18 and under are not eligible to use EURweb.com services without participation and supervision of a legal parent or guardian. EURweb.com is not a site meant for children, and we do not provide privacy measures designed to protect children when using the Internet unsupervised. EURweb.com also does not knowingly target children under the age of 13 and makes reasonable efforts to ensure that this does not occur across any campaigns it runs on behalf of advertisers or for its own marketing.

**How you can contact us about privacy questions**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or reach out to us via the info below.

Rabercom Enterprises  
PO Box 412081  
Los Angeles, CA 90041  
323.254.9599
